Guide to the Gay men's popular fiction collection, 1931-1992
Gay men's popular fiction collection, 1931-1992
- Giroux, E.X., A Death For Adonis, Ballantine Books, 345-32889-2-295, 1984 (Box 5)
- Glanz, Dick, By The Balls, Surrey House, MH 416, 1973 (Box 81)
- Goode, Marshall, The Chocolate Speedway, P. E. C., FL 91, 1970 (Box 52)
- Goodhead, Paul, Canvas Cocksman, Eros Publishing, SB-102, 1975 (Box 16)
- Goodman, Alexander, The Soft Spot, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1964 (Box 27)
- Goodman, Alexander, THE SOFT SPOT(Second Cover), Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1964 (Box 27)
- Goodman, Alexander, A Sliver Of Flesh, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1965 (Box 27)
- Goodman, Alexander, Carnal Matters, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1965 (Box 27)
- Goodman, Alexander, Handsome Is..., Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1966 (Box 27)
- Goodman, Alexander, Mercenary Affections, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1966 (Box 27)
- Goodman, Alexander, A Summer On Fire Island, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1966 (Box 27)
- Goodman, Alexander, A Sweet Gentle Boy, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1967 (Box 27)
- Goodman, Alexander, Blaze Of Summer, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1967 (Box 27)
- Goodman, Alexander, The First Time, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1967 (Box 27)
- Goodman, Alexander, Happyland, Guild Press Ltd., TC103, 1968 (Box 28)
- Goodman, Alexander, A Summer On Fire Island, Guild Press Ltd., TC106, 1968 (Box 28)
- Goodman, Alexander, Carnal Matters, Guild Press Ltd., TC107, 1969 (Box 28)
- Goodwell, Alexander, "The " Operation, 101 Enterprises, 101-2, 1967 (Box 39)
- Gordan, Alexander, Connected By Mistake, Numbers, 10016, 1978 (Box 37)
- Gordon, Howard, Chicken Camp, Surrey House, HIS 69181, 1976 (Box 74)
- Gorham, Charles, Martha Crane, Popular Library, 1555, 1953 (Box 48)
- Gorham, Charles, The Future Mister Dolan, Pyramid Books, G-197, 1948 (Box 53)
- Gorham, Charles, The Gilded Hearse, Signet Books, 714, 1948 (Box 58)
- Gorman, Meredith, Homo Playboy, Brandon House, 3063, 1969 (Box 12)
- Gover, Robert, One Hundred Dollar Misunderstanding, Ballantine Books, U7000, 1961 (Box 5)
- Graeme, Roland, Ravished Robby, Blueboy Library, BB 112, 1978 (Box 11)
- Graeme, Roland, Piano-Bar Pickup, Surey Books, AGR 101, 1983 (Box 68)
- Graeme, Roland, Family Man, Surey Books, HIS 69460, 1983 (Box 80)
- Graeme, Roland, Damien: The Young Years, Surey Books, HIS 69463, 1983 (Box 80)
- Graeme, Roland, Family Secret, Surey Books, SSS 119, 1981 (Box 86)
- Graeme, Roland, Hung Peter, Surree Ltd, HIS 69231, 1978 (Box 76)
- Graeme, Roland, Reform-School Punks, Surree Ltd, HIS 69247, 1978 (Box 77)
- Graeme, Roland, Prison Sex, Surree Ltd, HIS 69407, 1980 (Box 79)
- Graeme, Roland, Boarding School Studs, Surree Ltd, HIS 69413, 1980 (Box 79)
- Graeme, Roland, The Captain's Mast, Surree Ltd, HIS 69427, 1981 (Box 79)
- Graeme, Roland, Ski Lodge Studs, Surree Ltd, HIS 69431, 1981 (Box 79)
- Graeme, Roland, Star-Suckers, Surree Ltd, MH 484, 1978 (Box 83)
- Graeme, Roland, Whipped Cream, Surree Ltd, SS 038, 1978 (Box 85)
- Graeme, Roland, First-Time Trick, Surree Ltd, SSS 102, 1980 (Box 86)
- Graeme, Roland, Lusty Lifeguards, Surey Books, HIS 69435, 1981 (Box 79)
- Graeme, Roland, Easy Come, Surey Books, HIS69-606, n.d. (Box 96)
- Graham, Will E., Gospel For Suckers, GX, Inc., SP 106, 1971 (Box 29)
- Grand, Alex, Boot-Camp Trick, Surree Ltd, HIS 69223, 1977 (Box 76)
- Grant, Otto, Making The Team, Barclay House, 7023, 1969 (Box 6)
- Graves, John, Campus Gang Bang, Parisian Press, P 214, 1972 (Box 41)
- Grayson, Dick, He Knew What He Wanted, Piccadilly Press, PP-104, 1975 (Box 50)
- Greene, D. C., Midnight Plowboy, Rough Trade, RT 469, n.d. (Box 56)
- Greene, Jay, Behind These Walls, Midwood, 34-148, 1968 (Box 34)
- Greene, Jay, Tony's Room, Midwood, 34-981, 1968 (Box 34)
- Greene, Jay, Pretty Boy, Midwood, 35-149, 1968 (Box 34)
- Greene, Jay, The Cadets, Midwood, 35-164, 1969 (Box 34)
- Greene, Jay, Bitter Wine, Midwood, 35-192, 1969 (Box 35)
- Greene, Jay, Nino, Midwood, 35-204, 1969 (Box 35)
- Greene, Jay, Shadow Of A Man, Midwood, M-175-13, 1970 (Box 35)
- Greene, Jay, Cruising, Midwood, M-195-10, 1970 (Box 35)
- Greene, Jay, The Size Of It, Midwood, 508-60545, 1971 (Box 35)
- Greene, Jay, Men's Room, Midwood, M-175-35, 1971 (Box 35)
- Greene, Jay, The Size Of It, Midwood, M-195-122, 1971 (Box 35)
- Greene, Jay, Cruise Ship, Midwood, 508-60113, 1972 (Box 35)
- Greene, Jay, Chico, Midwood, 508-60613, 1975 (Box 35)
- Greene, Jay, More, Midwood, 508-60678, 1976 (Box 35)
- Greene, Jay, Behind These Walls, Midwood, 508-60765, 1976 (Box 35)
- Greene, Jay, Rough Trade, Tower Publications, 45-168, 1969 (Box 87)
- Griffin, C.F., Haakon, Avon Books, 43745, 1978 (Box 91)
- Griffin, David, The Wrong People, Paperback Library, Inc., 54-493, 1967 (Box 95)
- Griffith, E.V., In Homage To Priapus, Greenleaf Classics, GL 152, 1970 (Box 26)
- Griffon, David, Ask Ol' Buddy, Surrey House, MH 432, 1973 (Box 81)
- Griffon, David E. *, Asstrucker, Surree Ltd, SS 024, 1976 (Box 84)
- Griffon, David E., High-Ball Trucker, Surrey House, HIS 06904, 1971 (Box 69)
- Griffon, David E., Boys Into Men, Surrey House, HIS 06926, 1972 (Box 69)
- Griffon, David E. *, High-Ball Trucker, Surrey Ltd, SS 023, 1976 (Box 84)
- Gronowski, Paul, The Caribbean Connection, Blue boy Library, NIL 113, 1978 (Box 37)
- Gronowski, Paul, Against All Odds, Blueboy Library, 80017, 1976 (Box 7)
- Gronowski, Paul, The Caribbean Connection, Blueboy Library, 80029, 1977 (Box 8)
- Gronowski, Paul, Behind The Badge, Blueboy Library, 80034, 1977 (Box 8)
- Gronowski, Paul, Power Play, Blueboy Library, 80047, 1977 (Box 8)
- Gronowski, Paul, No Time To Care, Blueboy Library, 80052, 1977 (Box 9)
- Gronowski, Paul, Master Of Men, Blueboy Library, 80060, 1977 (Box 9)
- Gronowski, Paul, The Isabel Conspiracy Bk 1, Blueboy Library, 80070, 1977 (Box 9)
- Gronowski, Paul, The Isabel Conspiracy Bk 2, Blueboy Library, 80071, 1977 (Box 9)
- Gronowski, Paul, The Secret In The Argentine Jungle, Blueboy Library, 80078, 1977 (Box 10)
- Gronowski, Paul, Doomsday Machinery, Blueboy Library, 80080, 1977 (Box 10)
- Gronowski, Paul, To Kill A King, Blueboy Library, 80086, 1977 (Box 10)
- Gronowski, Paul, The Isabel Conspiracy Bk 1, Blueboy Library, CA 103, 1978 (Box 10)
- Gronowski, Paul, Behind The Badge, Blueboy Library, CA 107, 1978 (Box 10)
- Gronowski, Paul, Against All Odds, Blueboy Library, CA 108, 1978 (Box 10)
- Gronowski, Paul, Training Studs, Surey Books, SSS 124, 1982 (Box 86)
- Gronowski, Paul, Bizarre Triangle, Surree Ltd, HIS 69230, 1978 (Box 76)
- Gronowski, Paul, College Hunk, Surree Ltd, HIS 69242, 1978 (Box 77)
- Gronowski, Paul, Dangerous Trade, Surree Ltd, HIS 69261, 1978 (Box 77)
- Gronowski, Paul, Rough-Ridin' Studs, Surree Ltd, HIS 69269, 1978 (Box 78)
- Gronowski, Paul, Locker Room Jocks, Surree Ltd, HIS 69273, 1978 (Box 78)
- Gronowski, Paul, Bound For Pleasure, Surree Ltd, HIS 69409, 1980 (Box 79)
- Gronowski, Paul, Pleasure Slave Iii, Surree Ltd, HIS 69414, 1980 (Box 79)
- Gronowski, Paul, Cruisin' The Quarter, Surree Ltd, HIS 69420, 1980 (Box 79)
- Gronowski, Paul, Double Play, Surree Ltd, MH 486, 1978 (Box 83)
- Gronowski, Paul, Big Blow Comin', Surree Ltd, SS 034, 1978 (Box 85)
- Gronowski, Paul, Pleasure Slave, Surree Ltd, SS 041, 1978 (Box 85)
- Gronowski, Paul, Pleasure Slave Ii, Surree Ltd, SS 049, 1978 (Box 85)
- Gronowski, Paul, Telephone Service Man, Surree Ltd, SS 055, 1979 (Box 86)
- Gronowski, Paul, Desert Trek Tricks, Surree Ltd, SSS 108, 1981 (Box 86)
- Grosshammer, Ed, Fast, Hard Trucker, Surrey House, HIS 69135, 1975 (Box 73)
- Gurwell, John, Mass Murder In Houston, Cordovan Press, CDC 00072, 1974 (Box 14)
- Guy, Robert A., A Boy For Hire, unknown, -0-, n.d. (Box 89)
- Hall, Judd, Nazi Bikers, Rough Trade, RT 465, n.d. (Box 56)
- Hall, M & S, White Slave Boy, Star Dist., SS-1025, 1979 (Box 67)
- Hall, Mannie, Underage Dick, Rough Trade, RT 449, n.d. (Box 55)
- Hall, Mannie, Fist Rape, Rough Trade, RT 451, n.d. (Box 55)
- Hall, Mannie, Mean Marine, Rough Trade, RT 453, n.d. (Box 55)
- Hall, Mannie, Brownout Bait, Rough Trade, RT 459, n.d. (Box 55)
- Hall, Mannie, Punched-Out Dude, Rough Trade, RT 482, 1979 (Box 56)
- Hall, Mannie, Hot Cock Cowboy, Rough Trade, RT 468, n.d. (Box 56)
- Hall, Mannie, Street Trade, Star Dist., HB 501, 1977 (Box 62)
- Hall, Mannie, The Black Con, Star Dist., HS 507, 1977 (Box 62)
- Hall, Mannie, Bath-House Stud, Star Dist., SS-1020, 1978 (Box 66)
- Hall, Mannie, Brother Stud, Star Dist., SS-1027, 1979 (Box 67)
- Hall, Mannie, Leather Licker, Star Dist., SS-1029, 1979 (Box 67)
- Halman, Scott, Cock Hungry Creamers, Star Dist., BD 1008, 1976 (Box 59)
- Halsey, Brian, Below The Line, GX, Inc., TC 266, 1973 (Box 32)
- Halsey, Brian, Tool School, GX, Inc., TC 270, 1973 (Box 32)
- Hamilton, Mark, My Brother's Image, Avon, 0-380-82230-X-250, 1983 (Box 4)
- Hamilton, Wallace, Kevin, Signet Books, E 9970, 1980 (Box 58)
- Hamilton, Wallace, Coming Out, Signet Books, E7425, 1977 (Box 91)
- Hammer, Rod, One In Every Closet, Surrey House, HIS 69123, 1974 (Box 72)
- Hammer, Rod, The Male-Man's Bag, Surrey House, HIS 69134, 1975 (Box 73)
- Hammer, Rod, Trucker's Chicken, Surrey House, HIS 69137, 1975 (Box 73)
- Hammerhart, Curly, Cockrock, Book One, Surrey House, HIS 06931, 1972 (Box 69)
- Hammerhart, Curly, Cockrock, Book Two, Surrey House, HIS 06932, 1972 (Box 69)
- Hammersmith, Dick, Queers And Quickies, Continental Classics, CC-164, 1969 (Box 14)
- Hancock, Bob, Boarded And Bound, Surree Ltd, HIS 69204, 1977 (Box 75)
- Hancock, Bob, Dad's Hunky Lads, Surree Ltd, HIS 69424, 1980 (Box 79)
- Hancock, Bob, Trucker's Stud Sailor, Surree Ltd, SS 008, 1975 (Box 84)
- Hancock, Bob, Trucker's Stud Son, Surree Ltd, SS 011, 1975 (Box 84)
- Hancock, Bob, Sailor's Hunky Trucker, Surree Ltd, SS 021, 1976 (Box 84)
- Hancock, Bob, Coppin' The Jock, Surree Ltd, SS 042, 1978 (Box 85)
- Hancock, Bob, Big Truckin' Stud, Surey Books, HIS 69439, 1981 (Box 80)
- Hancock, Bob, Truckstop Hunk, Surrey House, HIS 69180, 1976 (Box 74)
- Hancock, Bob, Trucker Comin', Surrey House, HIS 69184, 1976 (Box 74)
- Hancock, Bob, Dad's Hunky Boys, Surrey House, HIS 69191, 1977 (Box 75)
- Hancock, Bob, Truckin', Suckin' Sailor, Surrey House, SS 004, 1975 (Box 84)
- Hancock, J. Robert, Memoirs Of A Combat Corpsman, Blueboy Library, 80018, 1976 (Box 7)
- Hanley, Mark, Saddle Buddies, Surree Ltd, HIS 69275, 1979 (Box 78)
- Hanley, Mark, Big Rig Truckers, Surree Ltd, SS 052, 1978 (Box 86)
- Hanover, J. D., The Boy Seekers, PAD Adult Library, PAL 509, 1972 (Box 40)
- Hanrahan, George, The Body Boys, Valley Circle Pubn., SV 106, 1972 (Box 88)
- Harden, Eric, Motorcycle Cops, Rough Trade, RT 460, n.d. (Box 55)
- Harder, Rick, Hung Butt Baller, Star Dist., HS 1002, 1974 (Box 62)
- Hardesty, Jere, Pell, Phenix Publishers, PR 266, 1970 (Box 45)
- Hardik, Lou, Chicken Tricks, Spartacus Books, SB-105, 1975 (Box 17)
- Hardy, Tom, Adventures Of A High School-1, Blueboy Library, 80023, 1976 (Box 7)
- Hardy, Tom, First Down, Surree Ltd, HIS 69206, 1977 (Box 75)
- Hardy, Tom, Leather Slaves, Surree Ltd, HIS 69220, 1977 (Box 76)
- Hardy, Tom, Adventures Of A High School Hunk 3, Surree Ltd, HIS 69263, 1978 (Box 78)
- Hardy, Tom, Tied Teen Slave, Surree Ltd, HIS 69276, 1979 (Box 78)
- Hardy, Tom, Slave Camp, Surree Ltd, HIS 69412, 1980 (Box 79)
- Hardy, Tom, Cock Stealers, Surree Ltd, SS 036, 1978 (Box 85)
- Hardy, Tom, S & M Bike Cop, Surree Ltd, SS 039, 1978 (Box 85)
- Hardy, Tom, Breaking And Entering, Surrey House, HIS 69189, 1977 (Box 75)
- Hardy, Tom, Adventures of a High School Hunk (Book One), Blueboy Library, 80023, 1976 (Box 95)
- Harkins, Sterling, The Voyeurs, Barclay House, 7017, 1969 (Box 6)
- Harlow, Sherwood, Soul Brothers, F.S. Publishing, GPL 101, n.d. (Box 17)
- Harlow, Sherwood, Turn On Turn Over, F.S. Publishing, GW 105, n.d. (Box 18)
- Harnes, Peter, Snowbird, Global Press, FGL 17, 1970 (Box 38)
- Harnes, Peter, The Arms Of Arum, Oasis, FGL 15, 1970 (Box 38)
- Harper, James, Another Room-Another Brother, Echelon, IL-340, 1968 (Box 15)
- Harper, James, Gay Brother, P. E. C., FL 43, 1968 (Box 51)
- Harper, James, Queer View Of Ted, P. E. C., FL 49, 1968 (Box 51)
- Harper, James, Gay Brother, P. E. C., FL 78, 1970 (Box 52)
- Harper, Rex, The Boy Buyer, Greenleaf Classics, AC 168, 1977 (Box 21)
- Harper, Rex, Slaveboy Brothers, Greenleaf Classics, AC 185, 1978 (Box 21)
- Harper, Sydney, Two, The Hard Way, Blueboy Library, 80019, 1976 (Box 7)
- Harper, Sydney, Murder One, Blueboy Library, 80048, 1977 (Box 8)
- Harper, Sydney, Two, The Hard Way, Numbers, NIL 106, 1978 (Box 37)
- Harriman, Preston, The Prettiest Boy In Dallas, Lambda Press, LB 103, 1974 (Box 33)
- Harriman, Preston, Ac/Dc Lover, Private Editions Books, PE 481, 1969 (Box 49)
- Harrington, Len, His Kind Of Love, Greenleaf Classics, AB 431, 1968 (Box 20)
- Harrington, Len, Stud Highway, GX, Inc., SP 117, 1973 (Box 29)
- Harrington, Len, Satan's Stud, GX, Inc., TC 230, n.d. (Box 30)
- Harrington, Len, The Midget's Giant, GX, Inc., TC 239, n.d. (Box 31)
- Harrington, Len, Jock And Rock, P. E. C., FL 34, 1968 (Box 51)
- Harrington, Len, Ollie, P. E. C., FL 50, 1968 (Box 51)
- Harrington, Len, Pansy Parade, P. E. C., FL 53, 1968 (Box 51)
- Harrington, Len, Gay Swap, P. E. C., FL 57, 1969 (Box 52)
- Harrington, Len, Ollie, P. E. C., FL 60, 1969 (Box 52)
- Harrington, Len, In Drag, P. E. C., FL 45, 1968 (Box 51)
- Harrington, Len, We, Three Queens, Phenix Publishers, CB 560, 1968 (Box 43)
- Harris, Brian, Gay And Happy, Neptune Readers, NR-156, 1971 (Box 36)
- Harris, John, Country Boy, Zil, Inc., NL 337, 1967 (Box 89)
- Harris, Kenny, Ballsout Trucker, Surrey House, HIS 69108, 1974 (Box 72)
- Harrison, Peter, Rock Hard Butt Lover, Big Boy Series, BB-102, n.d. (Box 12)
- Hart, Jonathan, Million Dollar Boy, GX, Inc., TC 279, 1973 (Box 32)
- Hart, Roger, Husbands...And Lovers, Surrey House, HIS 06903, 1971 (Box 69)
- Hart, Roger, Come For Lunch, Surrey House, HIS 06982, 1974 (Box 71)
- Hartley, Jon, Class Reunion, Star Dist., AGR 130, 1985 (Box 68)
- Hartley, Jon, High School Slave, Surey Books, AGR 112, 1983 (Box 68)
- Hartley, Jon, Call On Me, Surey Books, HIS 69471, 1984 (Box 80)
- Hartley, Jon, Small-Town Boy, Surey Books, SSS 120, 1981 (Box 86)
- Hartley, Jon, Backroom Piece, Surey Books, SSS 132, 1982 (Box 87)
- Hartley, Jon, Pleasure Boy, Surree Ltd, HIS 69417, 1980 (Box 79)
- Hartley, Jon, Man-Stuff, Surree Ltd, HIS 69422, 1980 (Box 79)
- Hartley, Jon, First Encounters, Surey Books, HIS 69433, 1981 (Box 79)
- Hartley, Jon, Slave Quarters, Surey Books, HIS 69438, 1981 (Box 80)
- Hartley, Jon, Carnal Urges, Surey Books, AGR191, 1988 (Box 95)
- Hastings, Banner, The Heisters, Blueboy Library, 80041, 1977 (Box 8)
- Hastings, Banner, Blackmailed!, Blueboy Library, 80050, 1977 (Box 9)
- Hastings, March, The Boys And Brigham Dee, Tower Publications, 45-182, n.d. (Box 87)
- Haven, Win, Male Model, P. E. C., FL 14, 1967 (Box 50)
- Haven, Win, Male Model, P. E. C., FL 61, 1969 (Box 52)
- Hawkes, H. C., Sweet Guy, Phenix Publishers, PR 289, 1970 (Box 46)
- Hawkes, H. C., The Long Gay Line, Phenix Publishers, PR 280, 1970 (Box 46)
- Hawkes, Samuel, Hard To Swallow, Star Dist., HS 127, n.d. (Box 62)
- Hayes, Adam, Balls Of Fire, Arena, DS 110, 1982 (Box 1)
- Hayes, Adam, Hot Greek Summer, Arena, DS 114, 1982 (Box 1)
- Hearn, Cal, Experiment With Men, Greenleaf Classics, GL 120, 1969 (Box 25)
- Heimer, Mel, The Girl In Murder Flat, Fawcett, 458, 1955 (Box 17)
- Held, Richard, Billy Banjo, Encounter Books, SB 114, 1978 (Box 16)
- Heller, Jess, Trucker's Load, Rough Trade, RT 474, 1979 (Box 56)
- Herman, Chuck, Bike Boy, Surrey House, HIS 06929, 1972 (Box 69)
- Hiers, Mark, Slave Boy With Fan, Blueboy Library, BB 119, 1978 (Box 11)
- Hilty, Vann, Hot Butt Halfback, Paramount, PP 112, 1971 (Box 40)
- Hinzer, Jim, The Number On The John Wall, Parisian Press, P 212, 1972 (Box 41)
- Hirschfeld, Burt, Return To Fire Island, Avon, 0-380-88088-1-350, 1984 (Box 4)
- Hitt, Orrie, Male Lover, L.S. Publications, GL 117, 1964 (Box 34)
- Hoban, Steve, Men Of The Bluegrass, Numbers, 10015, 1978 (Box 37)
- Hoffenberg, Mason, Candy, Putnam, 1042, 1958 (Box 53)
- Hoffman, Mark, Orgy Slaves, Greenleaf Classics, AC 225, 1980 (Box 22)
- Hoffman, Mark, Stud Star, Greenleaf Classics, AC 236, 1980 (Box 22)
- Hoffman, Mark, Looking For Mr. Goodball, Greenleaf Classics, AC 240, 1980 (Box 22)
- Hoffman, Mark, Come, Hustler, Come, Greenleaf Classics, AC 262, 1981 (Box 23)
- Hogan, Jan, Grabb Till Gladje, HSON (Stockholm), -0-, 1967 (Box 33)
- Holden, Ross, The Moment Of Truth, Blueboy Library, 80091, 1977 (Box 10)
- Holland, Kyle, The Coach, Surree Ltd, HIS 69255, 1978 (Box 77)
- Holliday, Don, The Man From C.A.M.P., Corinth Pubns., LB 1154, 1966 (Box 14)
- Holliday, Don, Color Him Gay, Corinth Pubns., LB 1158, 1966 (Box 14)
- Holliday, Don, The Watercress File, Corinth Pubns., LB 1168, 1966 (Box 14)
- Holliday, Don, The Son Goes Down, Corinth Pubns., LB 1177, 1966 (Box 14)
- Holliday, Don, Gothic Gaye, Corinth Pubns., LB 1184, 1966 (Box 14)
- Holliday, Don, The Gay Trap, Corinth Pubns., SR 602, 1966 (Box 14)
- Holliday, Don, Brothers In Love, Corinth Pubns., LB 1204, 1967 (Box 14)
- Holliday, Don, Gay Buddies, Corinth Pubns., NB 1857, 1967 (Box 14)
- Holliday, Don, Three On A Broomstick, Greenleaf Classics, AB 404, 1967 (Box 20)
- Holliday, Don, Home Of The Gay, Greenleaf Classics, AB 429, 1968 (Box 20)
- Holliday, Don, Rally Round The Fag, Greenleaf Classics, EL 367, 1967 (Box 23)
- Holliday, Don, The Gay Dogs, Greenleaf Classics, EL 386, 1967 (Box 24)
- Holliday, Don, Holiday Gay, Phenix Publishers, CB 545, 1967 (Box 43)
- Holliday, Don, Stranger At The Door, Phenix Publishers, LL 733, 1967 (Box 43)
- Holliday, Don, Blow The Man Down, Phenix Publishers, LL 763, 1968 (Box 44)
- Holliday, Don, The C.A.M.P. Cookbook, Phenix Publishers, PR 220, 1969 (Box 44)
- Hollings, Lew, Swede Lips, Greenleaf Classics, GN 400, 1973 (Box 24)
- Hollings, Lew, Bronco's Boy, Greenleaf Classics, GN407, 1973 (Box 91)
- Hollingsworthy, Llewellyn, Coq Le Grand, Greenleaf Classics, GL 151, 1969 (Box 26)
- Hollingsworthy, Llewellyn, Brothers And Lovers, Greenleaf Classics, PR 300, 1971 (Box 46)
- Hollingsworthy, Llewellyn, Naked Rebel, Greenleaf Classics, PR 385, 1972 (Box 48)
- Holmes, Jason, Ate Eight, Publisher's Consultants, BAB 102, 1978 (Box 49)
- Holst, Gorman, Man Rape, XXX Inc., GW 127, n.d. (Box 18)
- Homer, and Associates, A Bedside Odyssey, Olympia Press, no. 90, 1962 (Box 39)
- Homer, and Associates, A Bedside Odyssey, Olympia Press, no. 103, 1966 (Box 39)
- Homer, and Associates, A Bedside Odyssey, Olympia Press, TC-206, 1967 (Box 39)
- Horner, Lance, Rogue Roman, Pyramid Books, X 1119, 1965 (Box 53)
- Horwitz, Julius, Can I Get There By Candlelight, Bantam Books, S2911, 1963 (Box 5)
- Hossannah, Ross, Gay Vet, L.S. Publications, IMP 744, 1965 (Box 34)
- Houston, Joe Leon, Desire In The Shadows, Paperback Library, 54-942, 1965 (Box 41)
- Howard, Carlton, Daddy's Little Boy, Arena, MP 108, 1983 (Box 2)
- Howard, Chuck, Locker Room Lads, Surrey House, HIS 69116, 1974 (Box 72)
- Howard, Frank, Rim Rider, Surrey House, MH 411, 1973 (Box 81)
- Howard, Norman, Carnival, Carnival *, 101 Enterprises, 101-46, 1969 (Box 40)
- Howard, William, Caligula, Futura Publications, -0-, 1980 (Box 17)
- Hudson, Dean, The Lavender Elves, Corinth Pubns., SR 599, 1966 (Box 14)
- Hughes, Harry, Lock Up Humpers, Star Dist., HS 1014, 1975 (Box 62)
- Hughes, Madison, These Wounded Pleasures, GX, Inc., TC 269, 1973 (Box 32)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, The Wisteria Club, Blueboy Library, 80004, 1976 (Box 7)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, The Bright Young Men, Blueboy Library, 80007, 1976 (Box 7)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, Three Got Away, Blueboy Library, 80016, 1976 (Box 7)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, The Daemon, Blueboy Library, 80032, 1976 (Box 8)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, The Eyes Of The Basilisk, Blueboy Library, 80028, 1977 (Box 8)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, Garden Of Cruel Delights, Blueboy Library, 80038, 1977 (Box 8)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, The Executioner, Blueboy Library, 80053, 1977 (Box 9)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, Master Of Monfortin, Blueboy Library, 80068, 1977 (Box 9)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, The Amir's Harem, Blueboy Library, 80079, 1977 (Box 10)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, Phaelic Worshipers, Blueboy Library, 80082, 1977 (Box 10)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, The Monte Carlo Caper, Blueboy Library, 80090, 1977 (Box 10)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, Three Got Away, Blueboy Library, CA 102, 1978 (Box 10)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, Garden Of Cruel Delights, Blueboy Library, CA 104, 1978 (Box 10)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, The Daemon, Blueboy Library, NIL 116, 1978 (Box 37)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, The Mirror Chronicles, Global Press, FGL 22, 1971 (Box 38)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, The Other Party, Greenleaf Classics, GC 352, 1968 (Box 24)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, The Other Party, Greenleaf Classics, PC 1025, 1968 (Box 24)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, Stud Hung, Greenleaf Classics, GN 405, 1973 (Box 24)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, Come With Me ..., Greenleaf Classics, GL 112, 1969 (Box 25)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, Tangier 6-6969, Greenleaf Classics, GL 161, 1970 (Box 26)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, A Walk In The Park, Greenleaf Classics, PR 311, 1971 (Box 46)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, Graffiti, Greenleaf Classics, PR 324, 1971 (Box 47)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, Remake, Greenleaf Classics, PR 330, 1971 (Box 47)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, The Third Secret, Greenleaf Classics, PR 334, 1971 (Box 47)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, Strangers Can You See In My Face, Greenleaf Classics, PR 337, 1971 (Box 47)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, Something In The Blood, Greenleaf Classics, PR 352, 1972 (Box 47)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, I Am Dying, Egypt, Greenleaf Classics, PR 355, 1972 (Box 48)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, A Boy In The Night, Greenleaf Classics, PR 391, 1973 (Box 48)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, Gay Nights At Maldelangue, Phenix Publishers, PR 241, 1969 (Box 45)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, Seventeen-69, Phenix Publishers, PR 248, 1970 (Box 45)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, The Good Boy, Phenix Publishers, PR 252, 1970 (Box 45)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, Hard To Shoot, Surree Ltd, HIS 69240, 1978 (Box 77)
- Hughes, Peter Tuesday, Groping, Greenleaf Classics, GL138, 1969 (Box 93)
- Humparump, Larry, Cabin Mates, Eros Publishing, SB-112, 1978 (Box 17)
- Humparump, Larry, Cabin Mates, Spartacus Books, SB-107, 1975 (Box 17)
- Hunter, D. Garfield, The Wild Side, Blueboy Library, 80043, 1977 (Box 8)
- Hunter, Dick, Chicken Trick, Surree Ltd, HIS 69193, 1977 (Box 75)
- Hunter, Gabriel, Coxswains Of Malibu, Greenleaf Classics, GL 118, 1969 (Box 25)
- Hunter, Gabriel, Coxswains Of Malibu, Greenleaf Classics, PR 372, 1969 (Box 48)
- Hunter, Jason, The Flesh Game, Eros Publishing, GGS-105, 1973 (Box 16)
- Hunter, Peter, Kidnapped, Hamilton House, RAM 10-114, 1975 (Box 33)
- Hunter, Peter, Greasing Up Axel's, Surrey House, MH 478, 1975 (Box 83)
- Hurch, Charles, The Feel-It Book, Olympia Press, OPS 26, 1971 (Box 38)
- Hurley, Brad *, Black Master, Star Dist., WB 122, 1976 (Box 68)
- Hyers, Geraldine, The Bizarre Happenings..., Classical Novel, CN-112, 1968 (Box 13)
- Insley, James, Yours To Keep, Greenleaf Classics, PR 317, 1971 (Box 47)
- Insley, James, Trade Secret, Pendulum Books, 0445, 1970 (Box 43)
- Ironstone, John, Undercover, Blueboy Library, 80006, 1976 (Box 7)
- Ironstone, John, In Search Of Gold, Blueboy Library, 80067, 1977 (Box 9)
- Ironstone, John, To Be Gay, Blueboy Library, 80075, 1977 (Box 10)
- Ironstone, John, Orphan, Blueboy Library, 80085, 1977 (Box 10)
- Ironstone, John, Gay Rights, Maverick, EE 102, 1978 (Box 15)
- Ironstone, John, Gay Rights 2, Maverick, EE 104, 1978 (Box 16)
- Isherwood, Christopher, The Last Of Mr. Norris, Avon, AVON 448, 1935 (Box 4)
- Isherwood, Christopher, The Last Of Mr. Norris, Berkley, G-153, 1935 (Box 11)
- Isherwood, Christopher, A Single Man, Lancer, 74-913, 1968 (Box 34)
- Isherwood, Christopher, Prater Violet, Penguin Books, 1658, 1961 (Box 43)